hey guys this is a fun one it's not
super difficult but I kind of like the
imagery we got a palm tree and a penguin
and we're trying to figure out how tall
is this penguin together they're 230 and
the difference between the two is 200 so
let's give the height of the penguin the
variable X and let's give the height of
the palm tree the variable Y and now we
can write these equations we have y + x
will be equal to 230 and then y - x will
be equal to 200 in order to solve for
this we're going to do something called
elimination we're going to add the two
equations together y + y will give us 2
y the X +x goes away and 230 + 200 is
equal to 430 and then after we divide
both sides by 2 we get Y is equal to 215
and then next let's rewrite this y + x =
230 Y is equal to 215 in the place of
this y I want to plug in 215 and then we
can subtract 215 from both sides we have
X is equal to 15 so we now have the
height of the penguin he is equal to 15
units how exciting